hey y'all i think we've just gotten really comfortable we've gotten just really comfortable
everybody's just being really regular it's time to get fucking first of all i'm tired of y'all
thinking that i'm some talking head so uh you know all this talk about politics and all this shit
has become like the next um it's become like the next pastime it's literally become a pastime
like what are we doing it's time to get weirder everybody just needs to get fucking weirder
like yes i do i don't think anyone's acting like it's okay i just think everyone's just acting the
same being the same like i know for me i'm just i'm um i'm about to get weird i'm i'm just i'm about
to get weird it's i can feel it happening so you know well i'm already weird i mean weirder
i don't know what weird look like it just it don't look like what it been it don't look like whatever
it's been it looks like breaking from molds and order order y'all about to get fragmented thoughts
and art that's what y'all about to get that's what y'all about to get i was very thoughtful about
like making videos and content i'm over it if y'all get thoughts at all because i'm i'm tired
the the idea of being a talking head is just it's become repulsive to me that people actually think
that's what i am it's like it means i'm just like not doing what my soul is supposed to do
and that pisses me off y'all about to get this art and splice working i mean yes it is fuck what
they say but sometimes what people say you know ends up being like the the catalyst for you to see
some shit you couldn't see before you know what i'm saying and you're like hold up the whole car
the whole car is laughing because that's what y'all about to get you know i'm saying
and next thing you know because next thing you know you're doing some shit you didn't even really like
want to do no i don't want to do all of that stop trying to make me do ai i'm just trying to find a
fucking instrument to sample god damn everything tries to make you ai and sometimes you don't even
realize it's happening also buy my book buy my book buy what would the ancestors say and let your
brain start to really cook buy my book i'm over here trying to find a sample and this shit's like
taking me i'm like what what what what and then i realize it's trying to ai me bro so i need you all
to sign up for my newsletter i need you to sign up for my newsletter because i really i i don't want
i don't like instagram i don't i don't want to have to engage with this shit in order to let you know
that i'm doing dope shit i'm tired of talking to the camera i'm just tired of it all i'm just gonna
play the but i'm just gonna play it out yeah i'm talking to you like while i'm making a beat that's
the only way i'm gonna talk from now on is while i'm doing something productive other than i'm just
i'm you're experiencing me going through a real like switch up i am space i am boundary less
that's what it is i'm space oops that's not what i wanted to do i'm space that's what needs to happen
right there this man said i should be a rapper i am a rapper my pulse the inner rhythm that tempers
the cynicism i get from living existing is more than an organism vocalism never underestimate my
pen see i've been known to decimate divisions of the risen see i elevate the rhythm but that's what i
want to do right okay now i'm annoyed that i can't remember that verse real quick
my pulse the inner rhythm the tempers the cynicism i get from living existing as more than an organism
vocalism never underestimate my pen see i've been known to delegate i've been known to elevate
never underestimate my pen see i've been known to elevate see i decimate opinions because this diva's
on a mission moving with precision automatic pilot self-driven tricking the system into giving up the
goods of capitalism don't smoke the ism drunk on realism egotism never tripping on my own to view
the world this world with more eyes than two i'll be perusing through the bullshit i'm covering the
truth yes it's a dirty job of something that i gotta do my crew thick like southern chicks with soul
like afro pics born in the west and blessed the east of eastern politics six cents i'm holding
though i'm broken trying to find my way through the melee to tomorrow to change the pain of yesterday
okay kim martinez is over here giving y'all catch me i'm falling out of love with this music and
i wish lyrical skills message with records with a message yeah yeah i just yeah i'm i'm remind i'm
being reminded of who the fuck i am and it's very happy it's very exciting okay let's see where we at
with this i don't give a fuck about timbaland and i don't give a fuck about swiss beats the last time
i saw both of them they were on a boat with elon musk toasting and laughing and they posted the
picture on juneteenth so i don't give a fuck about either of them and i say that as somebody who used
to really give a fuck about kassim dean because that was my friend like those those paintings that
you see in my background when i'm in my living room they are on canvases that were purchased for me
by swiss i find it wild that so many people obsess over all of these celebrities who they don't know
and then you have like niggas like me who have been out here in front of your face the whole time
and it's like what are we doing am i cool with alicia keys alicia keys was fucking a nigga while
his newborn baby was at home the nigga was on tour with her while the man's but newborn baby was at
home still being breastfed so no and has she said anything about palestine no i don't fuck with
none of these people there should be a tambourine right there there should be a tambourine right
there so when i say it's time it's about it's time to get weirder i'm like i just feel myself going to
a whole other level of non-fucker non-give-a-fuckeriness what do you mean who leaked that about keys
we're talking about who leaked that it wasn't leaked dinner time that was just facts
logic will will vegetable pants be a track sure mel patel why not i would never use my pen
on that my pen is for the purpose of uplifting y'all that's it that's the purpose of my pen
it's dedicated all the women who've been swallowed up by narcissists that's who this song is for
for all the women who have been swallowed up by abusers and said oh shit i was never
this was never gonna work because i am space i am boundaryless incomprehensible the anomaly of me
so this way it starts here it starts early i am space that part is not supposed to go there
that's for the verse that's for the verse okay that's for the verse this didn't change its name
it ended small doses ended small doses podcast ended i did it for eight years
it's kim said where where'd that mic spawn from it's like sugato i am space tell me what don't
listen don't tell me what i should do i'm literally making an album you should use it as a jingle
i am space it's y-o-r y-o-u-r apostrophe i mean it's y-o-u apostrophe r-e but thank you
i am space oh i need to get those claps let's see if we can find some collapsing splice
let's see if we can find some collapsing splice
i gotta put a sub in there too you make a beat you sit here and you go through sounds and you make
sounds and you make you play chords and i like those okay so for instance okay you hear these
claps so what i'm gonna do is i'm gonna take these claps and they're not how i want them
so i have to get them so i'm gonna take this that's what i'm trying to make that's what i'm
gonna try and make it do we're gonna see let's just save it for now because i really want 16s
do you know what i mean when i say i want 16s
i am space the anomaly i am space i am bountyless
incomprehensible like it should feel like you are being cleansed like the clapping should feel
like it's awakening the like your cells to just clean out all of that i am space i am boundaryless
incomprehensible now someone here said steps from claps only and that brings up a good a good thought
because that's the kick and that's the feet what are you doing oh this nigga done hid his little
chewy oh wait who is val checking right now shout out to everybody who randomly grabs their titty
what's happening in mexico happening everywhere i can't at this point i'm just like i can't stay in
the heartbreak i just gotta commit to being a part of the solution as long as i can until i'm in the
heartbreak and then i gotta figure that out hola habana i am working on a design
for a t-shirt to do as a fundraiser to uh for cuba oh an airport shooting like in um
narcos i mean yeah the u.s probably start the u.s is involved in everything because the u.s is led by
an entire cartel of terrible people that push everything is somebody coming at val sideways
because val knows it all is protected space in here and she is now the moderator so watch your
mouth oh gracias frank west didn't need a reason to invade y'all none of this is like
they're just one of my besties today he was like yo at least niggas used to like pretend to be moral
now they just like got their dick out like i hope you are an upcoming guest on the jbp
can i explain what's going on i have no idea what's going on i know what i'm doing right now
i could explain that tired of explaining shit tired of explaining shit y'all i've done enough
explaining all right where are these slaps coming in right there jordi you better chew that chewy
jordi is over there murdering a chew stick
so that's why i that's why i titled this live it's time to get weird
because it's just i'm just over the the um the orderliness of things
y'all just gonna get it how i give it
why did you do that why did you do that why did you do that i know some of y'all are like
ma'am we never thought you were normal redo divide let me tell y'all something
i've been with a lot of talented men and can i just tell you all that i was more talented than
all of them and i had no idea who was alissa is that the ice skater kim said you playing the sound
after a mic drop is like a kid telling you a fact and cartwheeling that i love it what genre would
this be characterized in this is house but everything on this album is gonna be whatever
the fuck it is this album is gonna have everything and everything i am currently reading uh
a sky full of elephants and it is flawless and perfection and the patreon book club is also
reading a sky full of elephants and so if you were ever thinking about joining patreon this is a good
time to join and um at the end of the reading session which would be march around march 15th
i'm going to do an interview with its author
so reasons to join patreon you'll read books i know people used to come on my lives because they
wanted to hear me talk shit it might happen but get used to this being the lives me doing this or
packaging i'm just i'm i'm really like i'm an artist and somehow like we all forgot that
including myself the lax what do you think take a guess take a guess i am a cancer i'm a cancer
cancer burgo according to the tropic um tropical astrology what was i gonna do here
oh i was gonna read y'all some of the lyrics do you want to hear that do you want to hear some of the
lyrics do you want to hear it do you want to hear some of the lyrics i am not a leo there's nothing
about me that's leo the album is called political hymns person said wait did us leos just catch a
stray wait did us leos just catch a stray spend my entire life trying to fit the galaxy of me into a
man's orbit need to realize possible
i want that marker now i'm still learning how to use logic so sometimes that's right
amanda diva is coming back it's official as of today i spoke to my really good friend
who has known me for 20 years
and um i was like do you think i should bring back the name amanda diva
and he was like yes
both of my degrees say amanda diva seals thank you it's maybe thank you it's may
thank you it's may because i was ignoring it because
thank you it's may
it's may say
july 1st google it like what the fuck
that was the energy of google it there was an unspoken wtf
i am space
i am boundary less
the other thing that's with this record is with these records is like their their
flowetry feature
fuck flowetry
thank you rogers stay creative i'm gonna look that up
rogers stays creative
a producer named scenes
oh i like that name
anybody who did me dirty
it's it's like it's fuck them but it's also thank you
it's fuck them but also thank you
it's kind of like like shitty people
are to
empaths
what
germs are to the immune system
to like the to the to the burgeoning immune system
like it strengthens it not weakens it
when a when a when an immune system is developing
the germs are useful because they force the weak they force the immune system to
strengthen they put it to work and so as a developing empath throughout my
20s and my 30s i realize now that all these motherfuckers that was fucking with me
they were they were the germs of my immune system they were that to my empathy they gave me the challenge that my empathy system needed to become stronger and fortified so that i can
thrive in my 40s drive drive drive in my 40s even though the earth is dying then the earth is dying i'ma thrive in my 40s and try to save it so you know that's how you got to kind of look at it
one two three four five six seven
really that's a weird count
it is eight bars i am low-key delirious because i flew back from korea yesterday
and so i basically like went back
the earth is dying we're literally killing it
the earth is dying we're killing it
what you mean the earth isn't dying the fuck it ain't yes it is
we're killing it we're killing the earth
and and baby only one of us is gonna survive
and it ain't gonna be us
because the earth don't kill us
believe that
if we don't stop the earth is gonna stop us believe that i just i just want y'all to know that
in all of these dystopian movies you see the earth dying and then humans having to go somewhere and i just want y'all to know
the earth is gonna kill us
before it lets us kill it
okay
we're not saving the earth
we're saving the right to be on it
i just feel like we need to
we we
we are lucky to be here
what you mean africa ain't killing the earth
do you think that all of those african leaders
who are allowing
for all of the corruption
to allow all of these colonizers to come in there
and fuck with the goddamn planet
i mean and fuck with the goddamn soil
you think those
they're not african
excuse me
yes
there are plenty of africans killing the earth
the fuck
at some point
we have to stop looking at things with these like general lenses like well but the africans know
there are people
who actually care
and there are people who don't
and that's it
that's it
i don't know miss get it together but mj they gotta get it together
i don't know
because i'll be like
what are y'all talking about
like
don't tell me who to engage with
and who not to engage with
what are y'all talking about
okay roger
it's a full blizzard right now
you know why that's up there
you think that's up there for storage
no
oh let me block this person
i think y'all really don't understand
that i do not
have any patience
for folks coming on here
talking to me silly
i just knew you were on here yelling
go somewhere else
that is up there
because
that's up there because
there's a window
right there
and
the air
was coming from my neck
through the sides of the window
it was coming from my neck
and so i had to
i had to get creative
hello at
it
it's gonna snow all week
it's gonna snow
all
week
it's literally like
i think
they said
tuesday it ain't gonna snow
and then everything else is all snow
thankfully
it's not
it doesn't look like it's the kind of snow that sticks
but
that's what's up cj edwards official
yeah folks living in the city
oh
i don't live in the city no more
but all y'all new yorkers living in the city
it is absolutely hard
all this shit is frequency control
is weather controlled by the frequencies
is it sticking
hold on
i'm talking real reckless
jordie is it snow sticking
i don't want to shovel
i don't
oh i did get new boots
i did get new boots
and i got snow pants
so maybe
maybe that'll make it worth it
okay raquel says sticking is good
that means it's real snow
so we gonna
we gonna
we gonna lean into her positivity
you've been missing my voice
amid the chaos
i've been here
but i'm done
i'm tired of being a voice amidst the chaos
y'all got enough voices
but y'all don't got enough music
and so that's where i come in
there's enough voices talking
i'm tired of being amongst them
i was tired
i was tired boss
scroopa poopatita
which has happened
you gotta um
we have to like reset our frequencies
i'm not saying i know much
but my instinct is
that that means a cleanse
of the things that shift your frequency
and i know for me
that is a lot of like television and shit
which is why i am um
which is why i am fasting for ramadan
i'm not watching any tv or film
for ramadan
um
and
it's difficult
which means it's what i'm supposed to do
okay so let's see if this hook sounds right
i don't believe that i know how to make beats
like what the hell
i cannot believe i know how to make beats
i just like knew how to make beats
that's so fucking crazy to me
that i just like knew
a man has Tourette's and yelled out a racial slur
that's my thoughts
maybe i don't want that right there
yeah i actually want that right here
yeah i think sometimes y'all think i have thoughts on everything
and i really don't
some shit is just like
cozy
gymnastics
michael jackson
mama say mama
so that tommy matola
can come and sue me
why would i do that
now this thing is kicking me off
because you know they shadow ban me
it's kicking me off but i'll come back on
but it's kicking me off in 58 seconds
it's 57
50 seconds
so if you still want to jam out with me
i'll be right here
because i need to play the chords
for
did i hear sexy red michael jackson sample
that would require me to actually listen to sexy red
you